Finding Aid for Louis G. Redstone Photograph Collection, 1935-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Louis G. Redstone Photograph Collection 1935-2005, 1935-1977
Redstone, Louis G.
1 oversize folders
1 oversize volumes
6 linear feet
0542 Aa 2 UAm
Louis Redstone worked as an architect in the Detroit area from the 1930's through 1980's. His buildings include the Micheal Berry International Air Terminal at the Detroit Metropolitan Airport, Manufacturers Bank Operation's Center, Congregation Beth Achim, and the business administration building at Lawrence Technological University. The collection includes photographs of Redstone projects, as well as sketches, floor plans, and blueprints. His interest in art and travel is also well documented through photographs, speeches, writings, and newspaper clippings, as well as his original artwork.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
This collection was donated by Daniel and Barbara Redstone (Donor no. 9542 ) in December 2004. An addition to the collection was donated by Daniel and Eliel Redstone in March 2005.
The collection is open to research.
Louis Redstone was born in Grodno, Russia in 1903. In 1920, he went to Palestine as a Pioneer, working to rebuild a Jewish homeland. After three years, he emigrated to Detroit where he worked as a bricklayer. Redstone enrolled in the University of Michigan College of Architecture in 1925, graduating in 1929 with a bachelor's degree. Unable to find work as an architect, he worked as an artist and sculptor. In 1933, Redstone returned to Tel Aviv, where he worked as an architect, later helping to design the Palestine Pavilion for the 1937 World's Fair in Paris. Shortly thereafter, he left Tel Aviv for Detroit, where he started his own architectural firm. His firm specialized in architecture, engineering, interior design, and urban planning. His buildings include the Michael Berry International Air Terminal at the Detroit Metropolitan Airport, Manufacturers Bank Operations Center, Jewish Community Center, Congregation Beth Achim, and the business administration building at Lawrence Technological University.
Even as a practicing architect, Redstone indulged his interest in art, attending the Center for Creative Studies, and the Oxbow School of Art. In the 1940's, Redstone received a master's degree in urban design from the Cranbrook Academy of Art, studying with Eliel Saarinen. In 1978, Redstone was awarded the Gold Medal of the Michigan Society of Architects, the organization's highest honor. The next year, he was elected as an Honorary Fellow of the Royal Academy of Fine Arts at the Hague.
Louis Redstone died in Detroit in 2002, at the age of 99.
This collection consists of 5 series, Art, Clippings/Publicity, Speeches and Writings, Travel, and Architectural Photographs.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Redstone, Louis G.; Banks--Michigan.; Banks--Michigan--Detroit.; Bowling alleys--Michigan.; Community centers--Michigan.; Grocery stores--Michigan.; Libraries--Michigan.; Motels--Michigan.; Office buildings--Michigan.; Shopping centers--Michigan.; Synagogues--Michigan.
Genre Terms:
Architectural photographs.; Photographs.
- Art
  The Art (0.2 linear ft.) series consists of materials relating to Redstone's intense interest in Art. This series includes information on his exhibitions and activities to promote art in the community. Also included is a watercolor painting that was part of an exhibition at the Detroit Institute of Arts.
  - DIA Watercolor Exhibit 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Affleck House Restoration 1983-1985 (Box 1)
  - Submissions for book on Public Art 1978 (Box 1)
  - Art in State Buildings 1977-2005 (Box 1)
  - Watercolor painting (Folder 1)
    (located in UAm)
- Clippings/Publicity
  The Clippings/Publicity (0.3 linear ft.) series consists of newspaper articles by and about Redstone, his career, and public activities. Of note is a scrapbook of photographs and clippings documenting in part his career in Palestine.
  - Scrapbook including in part photographs of Palestine buildings and building construction, 1936-1948 (Volume 1)
    (include loose clippings dating up to the mid-1950s)
  - Redstone 1947-1961 (Box 1)
  - Art Exhibits 1950, undated (Box 1)
  - Art in Architecture (Box 1)
  - Book Critiques (Box 1)
  - Art (Box 1)
  - Detroit Art and Architecture (Box 1)
- Speeches and Writings
  The Speeches and Writings (0.3 linear ft.) series contains materials related to Redstone's published books, speaking engagements, and writings for the Michigan Society of Architects.
  - Interviews and Biography (Box 1)
  - UM Public Art Class 1980 (Box 1)
  - Speeches, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Writings on Art in Architecture and Public Art (Box 1)
  - Michigan Society of Architects Monthly Bulletin March 1959 (Box 1)
- Travel
  The Travel (0.2 linear ft.) contains documents and photographs relating to Mr. Redstone's travels around the world, for both personal and professional reasons.
  - Israel 1955 (Box 1)
  - Italy 1955 (Box 1)
  - South America 1955 (Box 1)
  - Japan 1956 (Box 1)
  - Mexico 1957-1963 (Box 1)
  - Israel 1964 (Box 1)
  - Holland, France, Spain, Portugal 1979 (Box 1)
- Architectural Photographs
  The Architectural Photographs (5 linear ft.) series is grouped into 5 subseries. The first subseries, Numbered Jobs, is arranged by project number, which is based on the date the project was commissioned. This subseries comprises the bulk of the collection and includes interior and exterior photographs of Redstone Associates projects, as well as sketches, floor plans, blueprints, and constructions photos. A photocopy of the Redstone Project Log Book is included at the beginning of the subseries. Many of the photographs were taken by Balthazar Korab. The Untitled Jobs are labeled with a negative number, which is based on the project number and the number of the photograph within that project. There is no title or date. This group of photos consists of mostly negatives and some prints of buildings and drawings by Redstone The "K" subseries includes prints and negatives of buildings and drawings done by Redstone. These are not titled or dated, but are labeled with a project number beginning with the letter "K". The "K" and Untitled subseries are not further described. The fourth subseries consists of photographs of Redstone jobs that are labeled with a title, but no job number or date. These are arranged alphabetically by title or category. The fifth subseries contains photographs of buildings and artwork that interested Redstone personally.
  - Numbered Jobs
    - Redstone Project Log Book (Box 1)
    - 175, Tom Borman Residence 09/1938 (Box 1)
    - 230, 386, 387, F. Poetzinger Residences 8/14/1939-11/5/1941 (Box 1)
    - 579, Style Furniture Co. 10/17/1944 (Box 1)
    - 691, Janet's Children's and Infants' Wear 8/24/1945 (Box 1)
    - 714, Lewis Bros. Funeral Parlor 10/4/1945 (Box 1)
    - 715, House of Modern Chairs 10/4/1945 (Box 1)
    - 764, Spitz Furniture 1/16/1946 (Box 1)
    - 798, Piemontese Society 4/19/1946 (Box 1)
    - 870, Peggy Ann Frocks 2/13/1947 (Box 1)
    - 899, B'nai Israel Synagogue, Pontiac MI 5/20/1947 (Box 1)
    - 933, Samuel H. Birnkrant Shopping Center 8/2/1947 (Box 1)
    - 934, Daniel Laven Residence 8/4/1947 (Box 1)
    - 936, Beth Schmuel Synagogue 8/11/1947 (Box 1)
    - 948, Nat Greene 10/31/1947 (Box 1)
    - 955, March Leach Lincoln Mercury 12/11/1947 (Box 1)
    - 963, Drs. Katz and Stammel Clinic 1/26/1948 (Box 1)
    - 978, Brothers Delicacies 4/20/1948 (Box 1)
    - 981, Perwein Pastry Shop 4/28/1948 (Box 2)
    - 986, Sholem Aleichem Institute 5/28/1948 (Box 2)
    - 993, M. Korchak Sherwood Market 6/23/1948 (Box 2)
    - 1004, Young Israel Youth Center 8/26/1948 (Box 2)
    - 1008, Temple Beth El 9/13/1948 (Box 2)
    - 1011, East Detroit Civic Center 10/12/1948 (Box 2)
    - 1014, Ira Rodman Baby Shop 11/10/1948 (Box 2)
    - 1019, Louis Berry Residence 12/15/1948 (Box 2)
    - 1028, Highland Park Public School Maintenance Building 2/11/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1037, William Berman Shopping Center (Woodward Ave, Ferndale) 4/6/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1066, Highland Park Nursery School 8/31/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1070, Dearborn Furniture 9/7/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1078, Margolis Furniture Store 10/24/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1082, Menenberg Market 11/8/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1086, Cunningham's Drugs 11/22/1949 (Box 2)
    - 1098, Halperin's 1/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1108, Speedway '79 Revolving Sign 1/18/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1109, Redford Center 1/25/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1112, Western and Southern Life Insurance 2/2/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1114, Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. 2/10/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1115, Nate Goldman, Furniture Row 2/10/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1128, Holbrook Market 3/20/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1131, Dr. C. Jacobs 3/23/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1154, Winkelman's (Harper and Van Dyke) 6/13/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1156, Dr. Manning's Clinic 6/22/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1168-B, Tel-Ford Shopping Center 7/30/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1182, Sucher Residence, Palmer Woods 8/17/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1192, Wilshire Motor Sales (Dexter and Fullerton) 9/28/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1200, Irwin Cohn (Telegraph and Fenkell) 10/19/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1209, Wrigley's (McNichols and Schaeffer) 11/4/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1217, Foods Warehouse, Inc. 12/14/1950 (Box 2)
    - 1226, Beth Aaron Synagogue 1/24/1951 (Box 2)
    - 1235, Richard Sloan Remodeling Stores-Wyandotte 4/23/1951 (Box 2)
    - 1265, Manufacturers National Bank (W. Vernor and Inglis) 10/22/1951 (Box 2)
    - 1272, Harper Shopping Center (Harper near 9 Mile) 12/3/1951 (Box 2)
    - 1276, Wolverine Tractor and Equipment Co. (8 Mile and Beech) 12/13/1951 (Box 2)
    - 1280, King Cole Market (Clairmount and Woodward) 1/23/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1294, Tom's Market (10 1/2 Mile and Woodward) 3/10/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1295, South-Allen Shopping Center 3/14/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1307, Industrial National Bank (W. 8 Mile and Schaefer) 6/14/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1310, Zieger Maternity Center (Livernois Ave.) 7/7/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1317, Wonderland Shopping Center 9/4/1952, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - 1322, Northwood Shopping Center, Royal Oak MI 10/15/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1329, Memorial Hospital (Van Dyke) 12/15/1952 (Box 2)
    - 1333, Labor Zionist Institute 1/6/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1336, Wrigley's (8 Mile and Grand River) 1/30/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1362, Cherry Hill Plaza Shopping Center 5/18/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1368, Federal Department Store (8 Mile and Dequindre) 5/25/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1370, Harlan Building, Birmingham 6/3/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1375, Seven-Mack Shopping Center 6/25/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1397, Michigan Liquor Control Commission 9/16/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1418, Darby's Restaurant (W. 7 Mile near Wyoming) 11/23/1953 (Box 2)
    - 1429, Manufacturers National Bank (Washington Blvd. and Grand River) 2/1/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1431, Holbrook Market (Michigan and Humboldt) 2/24/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1441, Linda Lee Apparel 5/25/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1443, Detroit Public Library (Grand River and Mansfield) 6/4/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1446, Bloomfield Plaza Shopping Center 6/10/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1452, Cadroy Management Co. 7/21/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1458, Sylvan Manor Shopping Center 9/9/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1468, Peter Pan Restaurant 12/4/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1470, B'nai David Synagogue 12/9/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1471, Wrigley's 12/14/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1474, Zolkower's 12/16/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1476, Standard Tool Co. 12/20/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1476-A, Pheoll Manufacturing Co., 10715 Puritan 12/20/1954 (Box 2)
    - 1483, Wrigley's (Jefferson and Iroquois) 1/30/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1491, Beth Aaron Synagogue Addition 3/3/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1494, Manufacturers National Bank (Whittier and Kelly) 3/17/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1497, Trenton Shopping Center 4/6/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1503, Mid-Michigan Shopping Center 5/6/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1504, Green Plaza Shopping Center 5/17/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1504-R, Taylortown Shopping Center 5/17/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1518, Chatham Village Supermarket 7/8/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1531, Cranbrook House Motel 11/29/1955 (Box 2)
    - 1545, Farmington Shopping Plaza 4/11/1956 (Box 2)
    - 1547, Arborland Shopping Mall 5/15/1956 (Box 2)
    - 1554, Manufacturers National Bank 8/15/1956 (Box 2)
    - 1564, Redstone Office Building, Puritan Center 11/15/1956 (Box 2)
    - 1568, Shaarey Zedek Synagogue 1/10/1957 (Box 2)
    - 1569, Fort Grove Shopping Center 1/23/1957 (Box 2)
    - 1570, Oak Park Lanes Bowling Alley 1/24/1957 (Box 2)
    - 1573, Western Printing and Lithographs 3/11/1957 (Box 2)
    - 1573-A, Nemethy-Davis Addition, Redstone Building (10800 Puritan) 3/11/1957 (Box 2)
    - 1588, Central Business District-City of Detroit 7/18/1957 (Box 2)
    - 1602, Dequindre Motel 1/7/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1606, Birmingham House Motel 1/23/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1607, Skore Lanes Bowling Alley 1/24/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1612, Camp Tamarack 2/21/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1617, Manufacturers National Bank (Cherry Hill and Inkster) 3/5/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1626, Prudential Life Insurance Co. 6/11/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1638, Livonia Mall 12/17/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1639, Gould Acres Shopping Center 12/17/1958 (Box 2)
    - 1640, Manufacturers National Bank 1/9/1959 (Box 2)
    - 1643, Scotch and Sirloin Restaurant (Cranbrook) 2/26/1959 (Box 2)
    - 1645, Detroit Bank and Trust 4/15/1959 (Box 2)
    - 1657, Berry Elementary School 1/6/1960 (Box 2)
    - 1659, 333 West Fort Street Building 1/28/1960 (Box 2)
    - 1662, Strike and Spare Lanes 3/19/1960 (Box 3)
    - 1665, Frankenmuth Mutual Life Insurance Co. 5/24/1960 (Box 3)
    - 1668, Redstone Office Building, 11000 W. McNichols 7/2/1960 (Box 3)
    - 1669, Peck Elementary School 7/11/1960 (Box 3)
    - 1672, Rose Bowl Bowling Alley-Windsor, Ontario 8/15/1960 (Box 3)
    - 1674, Robinson Furniture Store 9/19/1960 (Box 3)
    - 1683, Tamarack Recreation Center 1/21/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1690, Westland Center 6/10/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1690/F1, Manufacturers Bank, Westland Center 6/10/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1691, Alexander Graham Bell School 6/30/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1692, Krolick Elementary School 6/30/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1697, Yorba Linda Lanes Bowling Alley 8/21/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1699, Manufacturers National Bank (Fenkell and Hubbell) 9/20/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1700, Macomb Mall Shopping Center 9/30/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1700-J, Commercial State Bank 9/30/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1701, Old Mill Lanes Bowling Alley 10/16/1961 (Box 3)
    - 1709, Lincoln Park Renewal 1/16/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1710, Gold Bell Gift Stamp Building 1/24/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1713, Great Lakes Yacht Club 2/16/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1714, Blue Sky Lanes 2/17/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1716, Harlan Office and Warehouse 2/23/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1717, Oakland University Dormitories 2/23/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1718, DWG Cigar Corp. (Lima, OH) 2/26/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1719, Marina Boatel 3/6/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1723, Manufacturers National Bank (Birmingham) 3/26/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1724, Berkley Public Library 4/16/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1732, Manufacturers National Bank (15 Mile and Gratiot) 9/26/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1735, Wilder Branch-Detroit Public Library 10/31/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1736, Orion Township Library 11/9/1962 (Box 3)
    - 1744, Riverhouse Apartments 4/5/1963 (Box 3)
    - 1755, First Federal Savings Bank-Westland 8/30/1963 (Box 3)
    - 1756, Downtown Garage 9/25/1963 (Box 3)
    - 1758, International Village 10/24/1963 (Box 3)
    - 1760, Birmingham-Bloomfield Bank 11/9/1963 (Box 3)
    - 1766, Manufacturers National Bank (Sterling, MI) 2/3/1964 (Box 3)
    - 1770, Glazer Elementary School 4/24/1964 (Box 3)
    - 1772, City of St. Clair Urban Renewal 6/12/1964 (Box 3)
    - 1780, General Motors Parts Division Warehouse and Office 9/1/1964 (Box 3)
    - 1789, Manufacturers National Bank (Pleasant Ridge, MI) 11/12/1964 (Box 3)
    - 1796, Olivet College Library 2/16/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1802, First Federal Savings and Loans 5/12/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1803, Center Line Urban Renewal 5/13/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1809, Michigan State Fair 6/22/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1810, Northwestern High School 6/30/1965, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - 1816, Four Acres Shopping Center 7/30/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1818, Manufacturers National Bank (Sterling Township) 8/9/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1819, American Savings and Loan 8/10/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1821, 333 West Fort Street Building 8/20/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1822, Oakland Mall, J.L. Hudon Co. 8/20/1965, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - 1826, Wonderland Mall Enclosure 9/17/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1833, Detroit Bank and Trust (Wayne-Warren branch) 11/18/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1836, Southland Center 12/16/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1837, Riverview Plaza (St. Clair, MI) 12/29/1965 (Box 3)
    - 1840, Somerset Mall 2/3/1966, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - 1843, Oakland University 2/7/1966 (Box 3)
    - 1846, Norton Park Mall (Flint, MI) 2/26/1966 (Box 3)
    - 1849, Manufacturers National Bank (Westland) 3/11/1966 (Box 3)
    - 1852, Manufacturers National Bank (Fort and 14th Street) 5/6/1966 (Box 3)
    - 1853, Manufacturers National Bank (McDougall and Jefferson) 5/16/1966 (Box 3)
    - 1854, H.H. and S. Store Building 5/16/1966 (Box 3)
    - 1855, Manufacturers National Bank Operations Center 5/17/1966, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - 1861, Michigan Cancer Foundation 6/15/1966 (Box 4)
    - 1872, Manufacturers National Bank (8 Mile and Greenfield) 8/13/1966 (Box 4)
    - 1874, Jewish Community Center 9/7/1966 (Box 4)
    - 1875, Camp Tamarack 9/7/1966 (Box 4)
    - 1881, Genesee Valley Shopping Center 10/14/1966 (Box 4)
    - 1886, J.L. Hudson Co. (Toledo, OH) 11/16/1966 (Box 4)
    - 1890, United Broadcasting Station 20 1/12/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1892, Detroit Zoo-Aquatic Animal Exhibit 1/13/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1893, Troy Public Library 1/18/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1898, Scripps Branch Library, Frederick Douglass Library 2/25/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1901, Mausoleum 3/15/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1905, First Federal Savings and Loan (Van Dyke and Timken, Warren) 4/21/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1906, Wayne County Federated Libraries Study 4/22/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1910, Community Center (Fraser) 5/16/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1928, Hi-Rise Development (East Lansing) 11/9/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1930, Grosse Pointe University School 12/15/1967 (Box 4)
    - 1939, Hannan House 3/27/1968 (Box 4)
    - 1945, Dexter Davison Shopping Center (Telegraph and 12 Mile) 7/5/1968 (Box 4)
    - 1943, First Federal Savings 7/21/1968 (Box 4)
    - 1950, First Federal, Security Design 9/30/1968 (Box 4)
    - 1952, Beth Achim Synagogue 10/21/1968 (Box 4)
    - 1954, University of Michigan-Dearborn 7/7/1968 (Box 4)
    - 1956, Traub Co. Jewelry Factory/Offices 2/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1960, Botsford General Hospital 5/1/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1962, Orchard Mall Shopping Center (Maple and Orchard) 8/13/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1966, Village Green Apartments 10/3/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1968, North Hill Shopping Center 10/13/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1969, R.L. Polk Office Building 11/6/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1971, Jewish Community Center (Drake and Maple) 12/3/1969, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - 1973, Mount Hope Memorial Garden 12/10/1969 (Box 4)
    - 1987, John Wesley Center 2/19/1970 (Box 4)
    - 1995, Tiger Stadium 4/16/1970 (Box 4)
    - 2009, Metro Airport-International Terminal 6/26/1970, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - 2018, Michigan Bell Telephone 9/11/1970 (Box 4)
    - 2019, Northville Square 10/7/1970 (Box 4)
    - 2025, Lingemann and Lynch Schools 1/6/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2027, First Federal Savings and Loan, Sterling Heights 1/21/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2034, Rose Jewelry, Eastland Center 3/16/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2042, First Federal, Farmington 6/8/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2045, Dodge Estate Condos 6/21/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2046, Quakertown 6/21/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2047, Manufacturers National Bank Main Office Renovation and Remodel 7/9/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2050, Landrum and Brown Renderings-Terminal 1 8/5/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2057, Grace Hospital 10/18/1971, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - 2059, Beech-Daly Ice Arena 11/1/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2070, Feasibility Study-Buhl Realty Hi-Rise 12/28/1971 (Box 4)
    - 2084, Troy Office Plaza 5/2/1972 (Box 4)
    - 2087, Outpatient Care Facility, D.O.H. 6/5/1972 (Box 4)
    - 2088, Bloomfield Financial Center 6/14/1972 (Box 4)
    - 2090, Manufacturers Bank of Southfield 7/11/1972 (Box 4)
    - 2100, American Savings Association 10/20/1972 (Box 4)
    - 2104, Redstone Office Building, Livonia 12/14/1972 (Box 5)
    - 2104, Redstone Office Building Construction 12/14/1972 (Box 5)
    - 2107, River District Hospital 1/4/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2108, West Bloomfield Township Water and Sewer Building 1/4/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2114, Manufacturers National Bank-Renaissance Center 2/15/1973, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - 2117, Bi-County Hospital Expansion 3/12/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2120, Allied Supermarket Office Building 4/4/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2122, First Federal (10 Mile and Telegraph) 4/21/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2124, Fashion Square Mall, Traverse City 4/27/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2132, First Federal (Grosse Pointe) 8/8/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2141, First Federal Operations Center (Troy) 10/22/1973 (Box 5)
    - 2155, Downtown Saginaw Mall 1/28/1974 (Box 5)
    - 2164, ICL Truck Terminal 5/10/1974 (Box 5)
    - 2186, Earl Heenan Garage Study 1/21/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2187, Hampton Square Co. 2/4/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2190, Crossroads Mall 3/18/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2196, First Federal (Mich. and Outer Drive) 7/16/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2198, Water Street Development, Port Huron 9/28/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2199, First Federal, Birmingham 10/1/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2200, First Federal, Kentwood 10/1/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2206, Shaarit Haplaita 12/15/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2207, Riverside Hospital 12/21/1976 (Box 5)
    - 2215, Drummer Enterprise 4/11/1977 (Box 5)
    - 2219, St. Clair River Redevelopment, Port Huron 4/18/1977 (Box 5)
  - Untitled Jobs, 0.5 linear feet
    - Prints, drawings, and negatives of office buildings, banks, synagogues, libraries, airports (Box 5)
  - K-Numbered Jobs, 0.6 linear feet (in 76 folders)
    - Prints, drawings, and negatives of shopping centers, banks, hospitals (Box 6)
  - Unnumbered Jobs
    - Palestine apartment buildings 1935-1936 (Box 6)
    - Albert's, 14125 Harper (Box 6)
    - Fintex Clothes, 14365 Gratiot (Box 6)
    - First Federal Savings (Box 6)
    - Ford City Evergreen Plaza (Box 6)
    - Harold's (Box 6)
    - Hechtman's Terraces (Box 6)
    - Heliport (Box 6)
    - Houses (Box 6)
    - Interior Projects
      - Laventhol and Horwath (Box 6)
      - Fisher Guide Reception Area (Box 6)
      - Dow Jones (Box 6)
    - Redstone, Puritan Center Building (Box 6)
    - Redstone Residences (Box 6)
    - Shopping Centers (Box 6)
    - Synagogues (Box 6)
    - Woodrow Wilson Junior High School (Box 6)
    - Zieger Clinic, Livernois Ave. (Box 6)
  - Personal Interest Photographs
    - Downtown Detroit (Box 6)
    - Photographs for "Public Art", 2 folders (Box 6)